Curriculum vitae

Mohammad Amir Jamali

mohammadamirjamali2020@gmail.com

Mashhad, Iran 🔾

21 September, 1991 mm

GitHub 🗘

LinkedIn in

Blog ...

I hold a Master's degree in Information Technology Engineering - E-Commerce, and I have established a strong foundation in various programming languages. In addition to my programming skills, I have developed a keen interest in the fields of Machine Learning and Quantum Computing (QML). Furthermore, I possess a wealth of experience in successfully launching and overseeing startup ventures.

EDUCATION

Master's in Information Technology Engineering - E-Commerce Islamic Azad University, Birjand branch 09/2017 - 11/2019

Bachelor's in Industrial Engineering

Payam Noor University, Birjand branch 11/2009 - 02/2014

RESEARCH

An introduction to Quantum Computing; Advantages and challenges (6th National Conference on Distributed Computing and Big Data Processing) – 2021
English version

• Comparison of the local generalization error model (LG Trader) with the exponential moving average (EMA) in selecting stocks with the highest return rate – 2019 (Fourth National Conference on Applied Research in Electrical Engineering, Mechanics, Computer and Information Technology.)

Predicting Bitcoin price with Bayesian Neural Network by using COT weekly report(Master's thesis) – 2019 English version

SELECTED HONORS AND AWARDS

- Involved in finalists of UCL Hatchery Social Enterprise Award with Enviroble.Ltd (Santander Awards 2022)
- Ranked as the **second-highest** GPA among MSc students in the Computer Science faculty, with a **GPA of 3.88/4**.

EXPERTISE

- Machine Learning
- Microsoft Certified IT Professional (Network+, Active Directory, Network Infrastructure...)
- Programming Languages:
 - > **JS**: JavaScript, Node, React, AJAX, NextJs, Express, Redux, Socket.io (MERN Stack)
 - > PHP: WordPress Theme and Plugins Customization Full Stack
 - > Python: Web scraping (Scrapy, Selenium), Django (DRF, Redis, Celery, PyTest, Locust, Silk, Postgrsql), Cirq(Quantum Computing), TensorFlow
 - ➤ **MQL** (c++): Expert Advisor programing

WORK EXPERIENCE

СТО

Enviroble.com

Environmental Social Platform, supported by University College London

University College London BaseKX

03/2021 - 11/2022

London-UK

Software Engineer/Founder

Tradeoption.ir

Algorithmic trading platform to contribute to Stock Options Contracts Trading.

01/2020 - 02/2021

Mashhad-Iran

Software Developer/Co-Founder

Class724.ir

Learning Management System (LMS) to facilitate the teaching of programming skills.

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

05/2017 - 11/2019

Birjand-Iran

Partner

Daneshjooyar.com

Working on collaborative project, which paved the way for me to launch Class724.

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

10/2015 - 01/2017

Birjand-Iran

FAMILIAR WITH

AWS DevOps

System Design

Microservice Architecture

Jenkins

Git / GitLab

RabbitMQ

Github Actions

Agile Methodologies Docker

kubernetes

Travis-CI Postgrsql

MongoDB

Cassandra

Terraform

SKILLS

Collaborative

Flexibility

Studious

Positive Engagement

Initiative Driven

INTERESTS

Music

Workout

Travel

Environmental Activities

Technology

LANGUAGES

English Fluent

Arabic **Native**

Farsi Native